3045 already we turn them up yeah all
right I'm ready okay question of the one
what do you remember about the first
time we met I remember that I was gonna
be the cool one because it just seemed
more natural and then I spilled a drink
really all right yeah I was super
garrison I did wasn't expecting to be
all right that's what I remember
I can't believe that that came to my
mind first that's not the first thing I
remember it I would not have probably
thought of that I don't know what my
answer would have I don't know I would
have been awkward it was all awkward it
was very awkward the first time you kept
saying that I keep saying that well
that's just it you kept saying it was
gonna be awkward that I'm doing this for
the drink so it was like a way oh yeah
Wow you know I'm mr. smooth I'm gonna do
Oh Oh your mind I guess it's your turn
ah what do you love about our
relationship
the I don't know so far it's just been
the ease of it more than anything
because it seems like other people I've
been with and other people you date over
the course of your life it's just kind
of like so much goddamn work yeah like
you know and you don't feel like you can
be yourself and you don't feel like you
know you kind of feel like you have to
play a game a little bit and I don't
feel like I'm necessarily playing games
unless I'm playing games but then it's
kind of been put out there like we're
just fucking around right now yeah
oh when do you feel closest to me
they're closest to me when do we feel
close when do you feel closest this is
really weird too but I feel like when I
do something like work out and tell you
about it or have a hard day and tell you
about it cuz there's no one else in my
life like I talked about my mom and
mm-hmm
I talk about my family I talk about okay
trips and all that with my friends but
you're the only one I talk about like my
name I had a hard workout so stupid no
but do you feel close to me when you
tell me about it do you feel close to me
when we're going through it
no and I'm telling you about it like I
find myself wanting to call you and tell
you about it and then I afterward I
think okay that was I think that's when
I started knowing that it was like oh
this might be when you could complain to
me about your day okay
no I agreed agreed no it's good I mean
no they've been right now I feel really
close to you right yeah we have the
table looks fine it's like a jailhouse I
feel like I've done something well we
should have like a should be on the
phone yeah oh I'm sorry I think right
yeah hmm ooh you ready for this
I guess what are you hesitant to tell me
what am i hesitant to tell you right now
or ever ever I'm gonna go ahead and make
that call hmm I don't know it's always
difficult to tell you difficult if not
impossible to tell you if something that
you've done has bothered me like what
that might be me it might not be you
everything might be my perception of you
I can't think of one right off the top
of my dresser a little bit a little bit
let's be honest this is all about
honesty I think that sometimes you'll do
something and I'll be like
oh I don't agree with that but it's not
worth it for me to have that
conversation because it's usually not
anything big it's usually not anything
that I need to have a conversation about
it's like usually slept like shouldn't
just let that go kid is it my only child
maybe maybe I don't want to analyze you
but yeah but and then it could just be
me it could be my perception of whatever
it is and maybe I'm the wrong one and
then I don't want to have that
conversation either you know because
maybe I'm overreacting okay that's it
make sense huh okay good we're not
giving him surprises out here this is a
oh and leading into that tell me about
the time I disappointed you and how do
you feel about it now as if there were
just one time I don't actually I have to
be really on it mm-hmm this is a little
deep preaching like we're the only ones
here okay I think I've been disappointed
by so many people in my life but the
fact that you have so rarely like is
huge it makes me feel even more trusting
of you so I know that's not the answer
to the question but I'm gonna lead with
that having said that I think the
disappointment that I've ever felt with
you I've ever I think I've expressed
like and it's always really stupid stuff
right well I can't agree to that right
sure at the moment it's the most simple
well no like I've had a really long day
of making decisions which we obviously
talked about and I just want you to pick
where you go to dinner and the answer is
no I know that's so stupid but that's
the biggest disappointment you've caused
okay don't feel very disappointed with
you in general I'll take it we're not
very far I mean nine months then I guess
you have a little you have time but time
I can make so many more mistakes thank
you thank you yeah okay I'll pick where
we're gonna
I know it is but it is it was ooh
do we have enough sex enough sex is
there ever an upset um I don't feel like
I'm missing out I don't know but I don't
feel like I'm missing out on anything
there there aren't necessarily times
where I'm like damn it if only we had
had sex I think that you know and taking
the long view there's gonna be plenty of
opportunity for me to screw up and for
us to have sex for me to screw up - Wow
and for you to have sex and for me to
say no to sex I've never done you're
allowed to though you're allowed to do
that
it sounds some patriarchal thing where
it's like it could be better romance now
what could be sometimes I know that's a
bit let's see that's a mixed message I
know I don't know sometimes you you know
I'm expected to take the lead ie picking
where we eat for dinner but sometimes
you might not want to have chicken and I
thanks their dinner both there were two
tandem questions but yeah I think I'm
fine with the amount of sex that I have
I mean there could be more there could
be less I I'm not dissatisfied in any
regard okay yeah okay
it's all very good on that note that
abundantly clear all is well enough Oh
am I the best sex you've ever had I have
to be honest and say yes well we talked
about it before yeah no agree yes yeah
thanks listen I don't even feel like I
have to speak further about it because
there's like no comparison I do think
it's the connection which this is gonna
look away two years ago
I know forever somewhere joy two years
ago would have been like all the
connection has nothing to do with this
but I think you've proven that wrong
yeah yeah well it's not just me you are
a part of it I know yeah a large part
some would say more than 13% well some
nights it no
just kidding sure we thought you could
we keep going I was just you know 6040
you have to be honest for this okay
where do you think I may fail you I know
it's a hard one to deal with because
I've never thought about that I've only
thought of where I would screw up my
anxiety is more from like where I would
screw up rather than where you would
screw up I don't know a guy okay I'm
gonna have an add to it so I don't know
are we allowed to add cheese yeah well
take you go ahead like without comparing
me like specifically like in the past
what didn't work that maybe you're
worried might not work again it just
goes back to me I bet I think at some
point you're gonna you know maybe you're
gonna get sick having me around all the
time I don't know so I cannot fail um
you know you could be mean to people you
know you could be not welcoming to
friends and whatever but so far you've
been good okay I don't I can't think of
I mean
fail is such a deep like you have failed
me is so I mean disappointed but I can't
even think of a time where you've
disappointed me necessarily but fail you
you know I feel like if I had some
illness you would stick around I feel
like if there was some catastrophe or
some you know economic upheaval that you
would be okay or at least we'd find a
way I feel like we just find a way to
work things out okay yeah where things
would just work out because I feel like
so far in the nine months or however
long it's been it's like things have
pretty much fallen into place I feel
like I haven't really again it goes back
to not having to work all that hard yeah
I feel like powerful forces have come to
my aid you know so yeah
as weird as that sounds how do I take
you for granted I actually don't think
you do you do a really good job of not
taking me for granted
okay I think I don't know dumb but again
it could be that it hasn't I don't know
I don't feel taken for granted ever well
what if like you know like what about
not responding to your friends emails is
that me take you for granted is that
taking in a relationship for granted I
think that believe me I'm not fishing
for things I think that's taking their
comfort and like like their comfort with
you and they're your likability to them
for grant I don't think it has to do
with me I think that's part of I think
that's been my problem if you if they
took the time to reach out to you and
invite you to third party I've always
been under the assumption that they just
assumed that if you were going that I
was going to go to right and but they
didn't say joy plus wine which they have
right but now they know I get it I'm
saying that it might be an example yeah
me for maybe taking them for you know
maybe I did taking me for granted or
taking us for granted there's such a
thing as taking yeah you take it for
granted that I'm whither thou goest
cause die you have to remember they knew
me first thing go way longer right and
you were miserable horribly miserably
that's the story I've saved your life
I'm apparently sliced bread I know are
you okay with me sleeping with other
people no I mean other you've slept with
other people before me but and I'm you
know God knows we've both been around
the bend but not now well we had this
conversation that it wasn't what
I don't necessarily believe that we
agreed with the monogamy thing yeah I
have to say I mean that I think that's
the way you have to do it I mean I don't
want to sound judgmental but you know
like I feel like if you're more that you
do it with me someone's having a problem
I think if there's a three thing going
on it's there's always one person who's
getting these three in the bed
whatever yeah not three together but I'm
saying anytime you bring somebody else
in to like a couple I think it's
somebody out of those three people is
getting not what they're not being
served it I just feel like if I'm one of
the three it's not gonna work I can't
say that for other people I feel like I
can I feel like I can say that if there
are three people that are in a
relationship and even though they've
discussed it yeah and said this is what
we're gonna do and we can make this work
I think some of the one that one person
of that three isn't being honest with
the other two or somebody's disappointed
so this is a conversation I'm gonna add
to this chair so what if something like
happens like like we were talking about
last night if you've been to the Amazon
it's a true thing I just read a book but
it was a David Beckham had to get like
extra insurance cuz he was going to the
Amazon and there's microscopic fish that
will fly up yours yeah and oh you either
die or they came to me right being alike
to me
whatever it's called I don't ever want
to hear those words okay that's not a
choice I don't want that to be a choice
I all I said was I'm afraid to go to the
Amazon for that reason but you're saying
if that were to happen and you were to
find some solace sexually elsewhere I
don't know that's a weird situation and
I can't imagine that I would but cuz
it's not like you know I could do it I
mean you know it's just a weird creepy
thing yeah okay well I don't want to so
I think we're good but all right well we
could talk about it just know that I
don't think that you know I also wonder
like if somebody gets into a situation
with like so
he was married that's like have you
never seen a television show or read a
book or seen a movie it never it never
works out the Shonda Rhimes Oh what
would you do if I cheated on you
assuming it's already been done what
would I do I think that's all for me for
me okay go ahead for me I think it
depends on is it an emotional thing is
it just a physical
I know I know roll your eyes I I really
do like if you're absolutely madly in
love with somebody that you have to have
sex with them and but you don't want to
lose me I think that's unfair and I
would end it I think if you went on a
business trip and had too much to drink
and screwed up I'd be pissed right I
wouldn't want you going on a business
trip with said woman or man again but I
don't know I don't I I guess I don't put
that much stock in the physical cheating
so if that's what it means then okay but
don't do it let's not try it I wouldn't
know I don't believe okay I'm okay with
not doing it I you know point taken what
is missing from our relationship missing
I feel like we've only just gotten
gotten started I think we're still in
there like not the honeymoon phase
because it's silly but like I think I
know it's easy to say I don't feel like
I'm missing anything but I guess the
only thing we're missing as a couple or
in a relationship is further experiences
that makes sense like you know you
haven't live
together that would be something you
know we haven't gone through like a
death there's something together thank
God you know I just feel like there's if
anything's nothing's missing right now
day to day I don't feel like I don't
feel like we don't have any trust or any
of that stuff I feel like I can't I
don't know because we haven't had the
whole breadth of experience yet okay I
think I agree now that I need any of
those experiences what do you think is
the next step in our relationship
going to Mexico next week well I know
you're obsessed with knowing it's gonna
happen Wow yeah I what's the next step
in our relationship I think the next
step is not tomorrow but I think the
next step is do we want to move in
together and we've already talked about
it and mm-hmm when is the right time and
where is the right place and logistics
work I think that's the next time okay
it probably is yeah I don't really have
a list right that's okay you always have
a list but I think that might be the
next thing on the list you asked that
one right yeah yeah what are you scared
to tell me not hesitant that was earlier
are you scared to tell me I don't feel
like I have any deep dark secrets I
can't think of anything that I would
would be afraid to tell you
I mean well there I'm sure that you know
there would be hard conversations like
I'd hate to have to come home and say
you know I lost my job or you know I'm I
don't know I hope that wouldn't be
because of me I'm not saying because of
you but I'd still be afraid to tell you
because it's just you know I don't need
that in my life like any kind of
catastrophe I would feel bad I'm telling
you in terms of fears I think my it's
gonna be horrible just gonna tell you
a fear that I have had which is gonna be
horrible for you but probably silly for
people watching this is that at some
point you're not going to be there and I
will be there and your gun will die my
job yes and I will have to tell you that
she died because you will think that I
did do you think I'm gonna be at work I
feel like sometimes I'm gonna be there
when it happens
and I'm gonna have to be the one to tell
you that's interesting oh because I have
such clear visions of what's gonna
happen when she died - we sound really
morbid
but really do you know it's supposed to
be yeah it is she's an old dog I'm just
saying it could happen I know and I
desperately don't want it to happen when
I'm there and you're not I wouldn't
think you did it
I would feel a good thing somehow you
wouldn't say it but somehow you would
say did you feed her today did she need
something somehow I'm we're talking
about beers we're talking about beers
and this is the only one that I actively
had okay you know not every time but
like sometimes you go to get like a
pedicure or something and I'm there and
I check in with her make sure she's okay
sometimes in the morning before I leave
through work I like to make sure that
her chest is rising and falling okay
partly because I've I gotta get to work
I don't have time to do that I'm just
being honest was that yours or mine that
was I asked you okay but wishing that
again you will be irrational about it
you don't think you are now cuz you've
got this no I have a plan I know how
it's gonna or not everything is gonna
work out according to plan I think is my
fear in the back of your mind
are you scared that I'll walk away
always why the why I know it's why do
you think I would do that um everybody
does
Wow
how much time do you have right um no I
mean I think there are three people in
my life that I know or not I can ever
walk away and it took them years to get
there it took them years to earn that or
it took you years to realize it I think
it goes hand in hand
Noby and so I think as short as we are
into it I you haven't quite like died
out you haven't proven yet nothing
there's nothing to prove nothing you're
tested but well if these other three
people have been tested and won or have
been not found to be lacking mm-hmm I'm
wondering if they knew that they were in
the process of being tested or if it was
just all internally with you and when do
you know and was it something that they
did that they were aware that they did
to get there did you say okay well they
did it I'm just wondering how long I
have to work welp Jane okay yeah she did
stuff when I was a teenager that made me
go oh she's not going anywhere
okay Celebes been there through
everything right and I understand I
don't know I think I need 25 years and
then Katie who we're just like one we're
like okay so with her we went through
major life changes at the same time and
it just sort of happened that I was like
oh she she's never gonna go away
okay okay I'm glad for but but as I'm
saying is no length of association yeah
I guess it's like having been through
life experiences that they didn't run
and we just haven't had this yet but at
this point right now I mean you think
that if something should come up I'm
gonna kind of bait and go
I feel more comfortable than I have with
anybody else okay but do you think it
would need something like that there
have to be an impetus for me to go it's
not like I'm just gonna say well I'm
going
for a pack of smokes that's not good
because it's a 1960s TV no for a Becca
good for you
no I think it's I think it's just I
think it's just time I think I asked you
that yeah yeah who would struggle more
if we broke up I feel I would hate I
just feel like I would I feel like you
have like such a support group around
you that would be like it's alright he
was a jerk blah blah whatever happened
they would understand whatever I feel
like you would have people around you
okay to help you through it you would I
would have people telling me how dumb I
was oh yeah you screwed up I may be I
think I have my friends would say what
did you do okay
yeah and then I feel I would just you
know fall into myself you know yes just
grow the giant beard and you know just
be sad all the time yeah mm-hmm I mean
it could be you I think it seemed to me
it would be me
hmm which one of my friends have you
slept with I mean would you sleep with
have I slept with I don't think anybody
haven't there's I Jersey there's a
little piece of me that's like not that
I've been with the world but we do have
some mutual friends like I don't think
it would be one of your best friends but
there are a couple of times that I'm
like I wonder if he knows that person
from all right who would you sleep with
that was the second part never metal is
mad enough of them in now but the one
guys that are the straight guys that I
don't really know you just don't want to
say in today's no I really don't I don't
I mean Riven but you haven't met I've
met female friends I've met coworkers
I've met three guys that I would never
consider wrong with my friends like
maybe like no I can't even okay I guess
nobody I can't picture it myself so
don't feel bad I wouldn't want to sleep
with any of them there are stories I've
heard from fraternity days that I can
see if I were in college and we were in
college together
then I would have gone for that frat guy
but I don't know him I've never met him
I probably never will okay like I can
think about the kind of guy I would have
gone for definitely well now and not go
to that weekend this year it's curious
is Tikku I don't even know the names I
can like put the story with it but it's
alright it's alright
again like 20 years ago sir um what do
you think you would find if you went
through my phone right now
a lot of texts back and forth between
your people yeah I don't think my people
what do you like your texts bullshit
there's gonna be like a lot of that you
know just back and forth with other
folks but I don't know that there's
anything untoward that I would see if
you're not you know someone may have
sent you a photo of something I don't
know years ago but you know I've heard
stories that that's what people do now
but I don't know I don't know I don't
know that I'd find a lot of that I think
if you did ever get anything like that
I'd be the first one you'd show you'd be
like what this fool sent me I don't know
that there's anything crazy on there
unless there's discussions you've had
with your people about me what's your
lining what I don't know BuzzFeed lists
yeah boring stuff yeah married girl
stuff yeah yeah was that me that was
that was you that asked from you know
that oh what's the one thing you can't
stand about me pick only one and that's
a really strong phrase I think I think
that's the point
hmm everything you've ever done I've
told you instantly like smacking
chocolate ice cream there's no need to
smack it's pretty well I think you're
also too attuned to that and others okay
I don't pay attention to what other
people are eating on the subway or how
they sound eating it I wasn't anything
ice cream on the subway I haven't seen
yet and the comfort of our home and I
didn't realize that I was making that
kind of noise I think it bothers you but
you're the only person I've ever met who
it bothers um I know something it's hard
to say can't stand but something that is
of concern
could I I don't know I don't know what
they were although I feel like you don't
take out for yourself enough like it
work take up for myself and I think like
right now that doesn't affect me but I
think in the future it could like if you
don't insist on promotions and raises or
going out and getting another job I
think in the future because I'm gonna do
that every year every other year every
five years whatever well so see only
you're in a different level
professionally well in a different
purpose but why because nice because I
never cuz I do that every couple of
years I would say I want you to be like
me cuz I'm sometimes a little too much
go-getter ish then I think people should
it's it might also be what you do yeah
cuz you know that you can go somewhere
else and do that somewhere else yeah
fairly easily yeah where's I feel like
where I just stand on my principles and
say well then I'm out of here
you're you to have to be okay with me
being employed for a long time you're
right yeah which is I guess I guess I
would rather be employed and maybe have
to each and every now and then and not
get paid exactly what I think I should
be paid okay but it's also my fault for
working too hard or doing too good of a
job and then feeling bad that I'm not
recognized for it but that you think you
come home and feel bad about it and then
what I feel bad about it but I also feel
stupid for like you know yeah working
too hard at the place that doesn't
appreciate it but you know so can't
stand as strong but I worry I just
really want to worry about thank you
like that are you worried about me are
you worried about us in terms of our
weight about you you'll be good either
way there's more power in the
relationship you were me
power power what kind of power you tell
me I don't know I feel like you I know
what you're I think I am
I don't know that you think you have
more power I think that you think that I
delegate a lot of power to you okay I
think that you think that I sit back and
let you do most of the planning and or
you know and you think that equals power
I don't know about power I mean I think
that you know I don't know like you you
have definite ideas about things and I
don't necessarily one way or the other
so you win that one we do a lot of stuff
that you want to do and it's not that I
don't want to do it yeah it's just that
I don't have a lot of other stuff
demanding my time okay I'm free and easy
I'm breezy I'm good with it
I'm breezy I'm good I'm good with it all
of it so I think in terms of power I
think you know I think you feel that you
make a lot of decisions and then I
should make more power though you mean
well then what's your idea of it cuz I
guess I actually think we're pretty
equal cuz I think you know that the day
you decided you didn't want to go see X
movie whatever but you know I'd be like
oh absolutely which would be like you
making the final call you don't think I
do that now no but I think you know if
he did I would go oh absolutely
okay that's probably true yeah but I
also don't feel that I need to exert
that kind of power he's never there has
not been a there's not been in a
presidential veto that I feel I had to
extend on anything right you know I
think it's also pretty clear what I will
and will not do and vice versa you know
it's not like you know let's bring
so-and-so into it now
that I think we're good we're equal in
terms of that but I feel like in terms
of a lot of they're like a couple stuff
you feel like you do a lot of the heavy
lifting okay
but I guess that's a different
interpretation of power yeah is that me
if you could change one thing in our
relationship what would it be and why
that's not fun
if I wanted to change it I would cuz you
have the power
no cuz I've been in enough bad
relationships that I either just ran
when things got bad or flat things get
stay bad for too long that I promised
myself I wouldn't do that again
so there's any like changes to be made I
think I would tell you and make them
together okay
I think we have done that yeah we
haven't had any like major changes I
mean I guess the only thing I would
change is that we would both make a lot
more money and I mean work a lot less
like that's not a good thing in our
relationship it's yeah yeah it's math in
our power to do babe who'd be nice I
mean I can't think of anything clay yeah
I would want to change either but you
know we're still just start now yeah
okay
oh oh no I don't want to ask this if I'm
going to okay do you want to marry me
this is all been a trick it's all of it
your mom's gonna be jumping
where's they're eating they're gonna
play that Bruno Mars song do I want do I
want um it's a thought I know you know
we've had a discussion is that some it's
not something I need like there's no
religious reason to do it there's it's
not for the children it's not her you
know my mother doesn't give a shit no
one's gonna pressure me into marrying
you I don't have significant debt that
would tie you up so I don't feel like
there's a reason not to it might be good
for our taxes or it might be bad for our
taxes but that seems like a really cold
estimation of why someone would use
illegal agree with that you know we
can't protect you understood understood
and there's not that you know we can't
even really do the Brad Pitt and
Angelina Jolie until all can be married
we will stay you know that kind of
bullshit because everyone's pretty much
doing it now but for the most part in my
home state Wow
backwards ex that they are do I want to
I'm pretty sure that was question do you
want to marry me um yeah I wouldn't I
mean it's gonna sound it's such a
pretentious question and people get so
tied up in it and it's like a magic
moment but I wouldn't sure I mean I
don't have any pressure either way like
I'm not afraid of it I can totally see
it happening but I don't know what my
reasoning for it would be it is
interesting because we talked about but
I would also need to know going into it
that you would want to before you
propose yeah you spent the money on
their ring yeah
well all that aside not even the
proposal in the Rings I just wouldn't I
would need to know that it was you know
something that you and one as well we
would need to have a discussion well we
talked about this very early on like way
earlier than we probably should have but
it was like I want to make sure that you
know this is made for me and if it is a
need for you then we might not it's not
a date it's ever been Anita I'm
perfectly fine happy being
the unmarried couple you know the cool
kids yeah like I said it's never been on
my list it's never been there's no
there's no reason to do it other than to
do it and I wouldn't mind doing it if
it's something that we decided we wanted
to do or if some reasoning came up like
I think if we were gonna have kids you
know 1950s dad and me would want to say
okay I looked at married you know just
so you the kids can whatever you know we
were gonna adopt something I don't know
or if legally there was something like
we couldn't see the dog if the dog was
ill without yeah then yes but I don't
have any strong stirrings to get married
and does that have anything really to do
with you it's not anything having it's
their judgment on you or on us I feel
family I just feel like as an
institution it's never been you know but
of course my father was married like
four times
it was very dream so you know the
sanctity of it is in question it's a
joke
yeah I don't know I can't forgive any of
your okay
yeah I can't think of any of your
friends that I would sleep with I was
gonna ask that whoo it's awkward which
is whatever the question was which of my
friends would you sleep with I just
thought I couldn't think of anybody I
don't know I mean I feel like I don't
know
there's a reason for not doing all of
them like I feel like most of your
friends are gay so you know I don't
think Christina would be interested yeah
I thought you would say her
no no I don't know if I have what she
needs
after you know uh you know I've heard
stories but I don't know it just I feel
like your friends are your friends I
would let you know yeah it's weird
yeah you don't have anything you enough
I feel like we were kind of tandem and
answering them anywhere at least we were
in agreement I felt like the questions
were great but I can we're just boring
okay I made the joke that we're boring
mm-hmm I can't think of anything that I
need to know or you know oh do you want
to marry me can we do that one we can do
that one I actually thought you were
gonna do that I'm not saying that I
answer for us no I know I feel alone I
feel pretty much the same way my issues
are I do I do you want to ask that one
yeah well marry one okay so I feel the
same way mmm
but having been married for legal
reasons and not love reasons I also see
it differently right which I figure yeah
I like to have a reception I'd like to
have a party in a pink dress I figure we
can do that at some point there'll be
some milestone but I feel like that's
just the girl in mean that once all the
bride's Oeste know I don't wanna be a
bridezilla you would be I want a pink
dress yeah
what am I scared to tell you you can't
ask me well what are you scared to tell
me I'm always scared to talk about my
past
I always feel the need to qualify
everything and we've even talked about
that that you feeling you don't have to
explain it to me like the fact that I
married my gay best friend so that his
parents didn't kill em Gilles bench I
mean yeah like I feel I feel like so
many times between that and now so many
people have questioned me like they
didn't believe me like I think I'm a
woman scorned or that I you know I'm
saving face and whatever that I always
feel like I'm having to qualify it so
anytime something when it comes up I
feel maybe scared it's more of a dread
feeling but it's like ah I have to
explain myself to anyone and with you I
want I find myself not so much anymore
but like wanting to get like if details
of the wedding or the first year of
marriage ever come up I feel strange
that I've already been through that
even though between me and him it was
just so different than like what his
parents saw you know right so I was feel
scared too
I feel like you talk of we've talked
about but yeah like it comes up in
conversation and I feel like it's you
know I don't have it I don't it's not
something that weighs heavily that I
have any questions about it but you know
you're basically pretty open about what
the situation was and how it you know
and I know all the parties involved now
no it's just kind of a thing you know I
guess other than that I'm often scared
to run into people that that I've had
relationships with sexual or otherwise
why make everybody's like that yeah you
know I think it's always awkward yeah
but you fight I'm afraid you'd get mad
that's my prerogative well it mostly
depends on the other person it doesn't
depend on you but you know I don't think
that you would
I don't know bat your eyelashes and be
coquettish towards some dude that we saw
probably not 30th Avenue that you may
have dated before and you know I don't
know I probably wouldn't even realize
that's what it was until you mentioned
it later on I like oh I used to date
that guy okay yeah I only think it's
anything to be afraid of I feel like
we're really in tune which is why I like
that like us so much so I didn't really
learn anything like crazy there are
things I might I don't want you to be
hesitant to ever tell me anything
because I'm a Balbus so I do feel like I
might your words not my words I know no
I know I know yeah um but you know
that's how you are I do I don't know I
work on it maybe I should work out a
little more so it did kind of make me no
it's fine
you know however you are is how I only
think sometimes - hmm I would be you
know I don't know what about you learned
anything I feel like we're we're on the
same page for a lot of stuff and I think
that that's good and I don't I can't
think of anything that you know I don't
know why you wouldn't sleep with my
friends they're all nice people but no
we're gonna work that has another
question I don't want to know I just you
know should they ever see this it'll be
a conversation that I have to have a
place I'm worried that Chris Donna's
gonna see this now - now that I said I
wouldn't sleep with her but you don't
you wouldn't because you don't think you
have what she maybe well well you know I
don't know your stories around the block
I think yeah so what that's what I hear
that's what I've learned
okay yeah anything